http://www.muonics.com/Company/privacy.php

bottrapShopProductsHow to BuyDownloadsBlogFreewareTkPNGTclMilterRFC MIB ExtractorProductsMIB SmithyMIB Smithy SDKMIB ViewsHow to BuyServicesConsultingOnline MIB ValidatorRFC MirrorSupportDocumentationArticlesFAQsResourcesCompanyNewsContact UsEmploymentPrivacy PolicyHomeCompanyPrivacy PolicyCompanyAboutNewsBlogContact UsEmploymentPrivacyGENERAL. Muonics takes your privacy very seriously.
Muonics does not
sell, rent or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information provided
by you, the user, to any third party without your explicit permission or
otherwise required by court order.
To protect your privacy, and Muonics'
security, all pages on this site requesting or providing (to its owner)
personally identifiable information require a password protected user
account and a secure (HTTPS) connection to the web server. The Muonics
web site further supports HTTP Strict Transport Security (HSTS) to
instruct supporting browsers to use HTTPS for all pages and traffic
(including those not involving such personally identifiable information).
Muonics adheres to Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS)
requirements, including requirements for allowed (secure) ciphers,
and utilizes a trusted third-party PCI-DSS scanning service at
least monthly to ensure PCI-DSS compliance.SERVER LOGS. The Muonics website makes use of server logs that
track certain information provided by the web server and/or the user's
web browser including IP address, requested page, referring page, and
User-Agent.
Muonics uses this information in aggregate form only to analyze
the general usage patterns of its users only in order to make usability
and accessibility improvements for its users or to find and correct bugs
or problems with the website.
Muonics also may use this information
in order to take actions against abusive behavior, hacking, etc. including
barring abusive users from accessing the site.
Muonics does not sell, rent or
disclose any personally identifiable information from these logs to third
parties.
Muonics may provide, at its sole discretion, purely aggregate
information from these logs to third parties as required to conduct its
business.USER ACCOUNTS. Users of the Muonics website are permitted to create a
personal user account.
Muonics requires only that a valid email address be
provided when creating the account.
The user may, at his or her discretion,
provide further "Profile" information with their account, including name,
organization, postal address, and phone number.
This information is used for
administrative purposes only to provide customer support and as a
point of contact to resolve any possible copyright or trademark infringement
disputes over user-submitted Resource/FAQ area submissions.
Muonics does not
use the provided information to send advertisements of any kind except as
a response to a customer inquiry/request for such information.
Muonics does
not sell, rent or otherwise disclose this information to third parties
without your explicit permission.SUPPORT. Muonics may request information from users of its website or
software in response to customer support inquiries as required in order to
properly diagnose and resolve the issue adequately and promptly.
Muonics
may retain such information in the form of bug databases and email logs for
historical purposes.
Muonics does not disclose proprietary or personally
identifiable information provided by the user in this process to third
parties.
Muonics may choose to make available to its users
non-personally-identifiable information, such as problem symptoms and
resolution, that it deems appropriate for other users who may encounter
similar issues.SALES. Muonics collects certain personally identifiable information,
such as name, organization, postal address, telephone number, and credit
card/payment information, in order to fulfill orders submitted by users
either via its website or by quote/purchase order.
Muonics does not disclose
any such private or personally identifiable information to any third party
except as required to complete the requested order.
Namely, this information
may be provided to AUTHORIZE.NET(R), Muonics' credit card processing gateway,
and/or to Wells Fargo Bank, for authorization and transaction settlement
purposes.
By placing an order with Muonics, you understand that this is a
necessary procedure for processing the order, and your order placement
constitutes explicit permission to use the information in this manner.Muonics may retain portions of this information as for historical purposes,
as required to fulfill any obligations with regards to terms of warranty or
return policy explained in the license agreement(s) for the purchased
product(s), for fraud protection, or as required by law.
Muonics retains
only enough payment information as is required to fulfill these obligations,
and measures are taken to protect this information from unauthorized access.
For auditing purposes, information is retained for a minimum of five (5)
years from the date of purchase.If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact privacy@muonics.com or write Muonics at the postal address given on the Contact Page.Site MapViewing TipsPrivacyCopyright © 2020 Muonics, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Muonics, MIB Smithy, MIB Views, and their respective logos are trademarks of Muonics, Inc.
